<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jereme Causing</title>
    <link>https://jeremecausing.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jereme Causing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:06:27 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jeremecausing.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Signs of a &#34;Fake Programmer&#34;</title>
      <link>https://jeremecausing.com/post/signs-of-a-fake-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:06:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremecausing.com/post/signs-of-a-fake-programmer/</guid>
      <description>Programming is not just a skill, it’s a mindset. I’m not saying a programmer has to be a perfect coder but there are some aspects that one needs to prove especially when facing difficult scenarios.
Despite of having a very good candidate screening, there are still a lot of instances where event the best intensions of the organization cannot prevent having programmers who don&amp;rsquo;t even seem to fit in.
Based on my experience, this the list of some traits in people who can be considered a &amp;ldquo;fake programmer&amp;rdquo;:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devcon Summit PH 2017: A Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://jeremecausing.com/post/devcon-summit-ph-2017-a-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 13:53:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremecausing.com/post/devcon-summit-ph-2017-a-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Devcon, a non-profit organization that aids developers, held it&amp;rsquo;s 2-day summit last November 18, 2017 at SM Aura, BGC, Taguig. The theme is &amp;ldquo;Changing the Game&amp;rdquo; which refers to the main topics the event is divided into four groups, namely Blockchain, Devops, AI, and Cybersecurity. These fields are known to be the current game changers and offers new career paths.
Blockchains This field offered new opportunities in the industry apart from cryptocurrencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Distributed Version Control Systems</title>
      <link>https://jeremecausing.com/post/the-importance-of-distributed-version-control-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremecausing.com/post/the-importance-of-distributed-version-control-systems/</guid>
      <description>These days, the use of Distributed Version Control Systems (DVCS) has become a standard in most large products. It is an automated to save a lot of tasks, and resources such as disk space.
What is DVCS?
For those who don’t know what distributed version control is, it is an automated way of storing changes on your code while collaborating with other programmers under that shared project. Think of it as creating backup copies of your project on your drive (and probably adding dates on your compressed folders) and merging your latest code with your teammate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>